<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-04-20T16:33:47+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Builtable Coworking Website</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Building a Cashless Community</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/Building-a-Cashless-Community-through-gcash.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Building a Cashless Community" /><published>2018-04-08T15:23:52+08:00</published><updated>2018-04-08T15:23:52+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/Building-a-Cashless-Community-through-gcash</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/Building-a-Cashless-Community-through-gcash.html">&lt;p&gt;“Ang malas! Naiwan ko ulit wallet ko!” - Do you always forget your wallet at home? Don’t you get annoyed when the only payment schemes of an establishment is through bank deposit or cash? Worry no more! This is the cashless generation through GCash! You can now use your mobile phone as an e-wallet!
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
A GCash sticker on a door signifies that this a cashless establishment.
&lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blogs/gcash/gcash4.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The company offers their ‘Scan to Pay’ feature via GCash QR as main mode of payment for dining, shopping and other services. 
&lt;br /&gt;
It only takes 4 easy steps for you to purchase:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on ‘Pay QR’ button.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blogs/gcash/gcash3.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scan the QR code of the establishment.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blogs/gcash/gcash2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enter the amount you wanted to pay for the service/s availed.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finally, confirm the payment.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blogs/gcash/gcash1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once these are done, you’ll be receiving an SMS that the payment is complete.&lt;br /&gt; Isn’t it so cool and convenient??
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Here in Builtable, we believe that through this cashless system ANYONE can purchase digitally. Whether you have or don’t have a credit card, just through your mobile phone, you have the power to purchase. Ultimately, it’s another platform that levels the playing field for small businesses and consumers.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
But wait, there’s more! Until December 2018, all transactions using GCash will have a 10% cashback! 10%!!
&lt;br /&gt;
For example, if you will avail our day rate coworking space, from 300 PHP it becomes 270 PHP!
&lt;br /&gt; 
&lt;br /&gt;
Now, what are you waiting for? Let’s turn this country into a cashless community! Be part of this by visiting: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mynt.xyz/&quot;&gt;https://www.mynt.xyz/&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Don’t have a GCash account yet? Start &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gcash.com/personal/getting-started&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;small&gt;
&lt;i&gt;
Builtable Coworking offers &lt;a href=&quot;https://builtable.co/coworking#services&quot;&gt;office spaces&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://builtable.co/coworking#services&quot;&gt;coworking spaces&lt;/a&gt;, comaking and events space in Mandaluyong City Manila, Philippines!
&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">“Ang malas! Naiwan ko ulit wallet ko!” - Do you always forget your wallet at home? Don’t you get annoyed when the only payment schemes of an establishment is through bank deposit or cash? Worry no more! This is the cashless generation through GCash! You can now use your mobile phone as an e-wallet! A GCash sticker on a door signifies that this a cashless establishment. The company offers their ‘Scan to Pay’ feature via GCash QR as main mode of payment for dining, shopping and other services. It only takes 4 easy steps for you to purchase: Click on ‘Pay QR’ button. Scan the QR code of the establishment. Enter the amount you wanted to pay for the service/s availed. Finally, confirm the payment.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Customized food molds using Vaquform!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/Vaquforming-in-Builtable.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Customized food molds using Vaquform!" /><published>2018-03-17T15:33:52+08:00</published><updated>2018-03-17T15:33:52+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/Vaquforming-in-Builtable</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/Vaquforming-in-Builtable.html">&lt;p&gt;Have you ever thought of giving someone customized chocolates? Well, John Tan, inventor of Vaquform, can show you how to do it! With just the use of clay, plastic sheets (food grade) and vacuum forming, people were able to make their own chocolate mold in a matter of seconds!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blogs/Vaquform/vaquform-workshop.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Here’s a sample of the actual mold that one of the participants made! Someone can now make leaves-shaped chocolates wherever, whenever!
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/blogs/Vaquform/chocolate-leaf-mold.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This may look futuristic and high-tech, but according to John, the technology has been there ever since! He just shrunk the clunky machine to be more sleek and compact, making vaquform useful and stylish at the same time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To know more about Vaquform, visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vaquform.com/&quot;&gt;vaquform.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;854&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; class=&quot;youtube-video&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hISq5XGbdhE&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This workshop is actually one of the workshops we do here in Builtable Coworking. Want to learn something new on weekends? For more of our workshops follow our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/builtable/events&quot;&gt;Facebook Events page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;small&gt;
&lt;i&gt;
Builtable Coworking offers &lt;a href=&quot;https://builtable.co/coworking#services&quot;&gt;office spaces&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://builtable.co/coworking#services&quot;&gt;coworking spaces&lt;/a&gt;, comaking and events space in Mandaluyong City Manila, Philippines!
&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Have you ever thought of giving someone customized chocolates? Well, John Tan, inventor of Vaquform, can show you how to do it! With just the use of clay, plastic sheets (food grade) and vacuum forming, people were able to make their own chocolate mold in a matter of seconds!</summary></entry></feed>